

# Adrianov Pavel

Male, 31 year, born on 11 August 1987

+7 (978) 7143075

pavel@adrianov.pro — preferred means of communication

Skype: adrianovpavel

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pavel-adrianov/

Another site: http://adrianov.pro

Reside in: Simferopol

Citizenship: Ukraine, work permit at: Russia, Ukraine

Ready to relocate, ready for business trips

Desired position and salary

# Data Scientist. Python developer.

3 500

HSD

IT, Internet, Telecom

- Software Development
- Networks
- Project Management

Employment: project work, part time, full time

Work schedule: remote working, flexible schedule, full day, shift schedule

Desired travel time to work: any

## Work experience — 12 years 3 months

August 2015 — till now

3 years 4 months

# **TireConnect**

Ukraine

Software developer. Data scientist.

Develop and support huge e-commerce project.

January 2013 — January 2015 2 years 1 month

#### **TeamAve**

Simferopol

#### PHP developer

Working on a large ecommerce project. Was involved in the integration of payment systems, scaling the project, optimizing for high loads.

December 2011 — December 2013 2 years 1 month

#### ameria GmbH

Simferopol, ameria.de

PHP developer. Team Lead.

Was engaged in the development of large projects on Symfony2.

June 2009 — November 2011 2 years 6 months

# **NewVision**

Simferopol

# PHP developer

The work was carried out over several high-load projects with large volumes of data (Exchange of links, Multithreaded indexing of third-party web-sites, processing of large amounts of data).

April 2008 — September 2009 1 year 6 months

### depositfiles.com

Kyiv, depositfiles.com

## PHP developer

The responsibility was to optimize databases for high loads (postgresql, mysql), code optimization, load distribution on servers, setting up nginx, redis.

November 2007 — March 2008 5 months

#### skidki-ua.com

Kyiv, skidki-ua.com

#### Team leader

Lead developer of the project skidki-ua.com. The project developed by me on symfony 1.4.

January 2006 — August 2007 1 year 8 months

#### **Freelance**

# PHP developer

Worked as a freelancer. Carried out orders for various CMS (RunCMS, Joomla, Typo3, WordPress, etc)

#### Education

## Higher

2009

# Vernadsky Taurida National University, Simferopol

Faculty of Mathematics, Apply Math

#### Key skills

Languages

Russian — native

English — I can attend an interview Ukrainian — I am a fluent speaker

Skills

Machine Leaning Big Data Data Analysis Python Symfony Nginx PHP MongoDB

#### Further information

About me

Senior software developer with 12 year of solid experience in IT. My main passion for now is machine learning and data science. Also I have a lot of experience in PHP and Python development. Looking for product manager, team leader, data-scientist position. I am familar with machine learning algorithms and python libraries such as Pandas, Numpy, Scikit-learn, XGBoost, etc. Also I have a lot of experience with PHP frameworks such as Symfony and Laravel. I have build several highload and big data projects.

Design Patterns

Redis

Checkout my accomplishments and certificates:

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/7YVTA6XT5Z9H - Machine Learning and Data Science Specialization.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/3MCLDSDVCQRY - Introduction to Machine Learning.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/TAP4VKTPCLP8 - Big Data Analysis: Hive, Spark SQL, DataFrames and GraphFrames.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/W59WWG5P47VF - Big Data Essentials: HDFS, MapReduce and Spark RDD.

One of my hobby is creating devices on arduino or raspberry. For example: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CHe23H-Dpm4

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6osE\_LyXUqc

I'm fond of rock music, fantastic literature and mountain skiing.

You can contact with me via email for hiring or any other questions.